

CONTACT

+263 78 372 6458

confidencenyirenda7@gmail.com

Q 42 Ceres Road, Avondale

github.com/renegadec

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript(ES6)
- ReactJS, Redux, JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Figma
- SQL, MySQL, MongoDB
- GIT, NPM
- Python

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE

Hons. Computer Science 2013 - 2016

MOOC IN DIGITAL CURRENCIES

University of Nicosia 2019

CONFIDENCE NYIRENDA

WEB DEVELOPER

INTRODUCTION

I am a frontend web developer(working to be a full-stack one day) from Harare, Zimbabwe, who loves Programming, Developing, Learning and Problem Solving. I am passionate about taking risks and solving them by Communicating & Sharing experience and knowledge.

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

GOLIX.IO

2016 - 2017

- Designed cryptocurrency exchange interface
- Testing and maintenance of platform that scaled
- Versioning documentation

WEB DEVELOPER

SMARTCASH

2017 - MAY 2019

- Design of Smartcash web-wallet
- Collaborated on designs that match competitors' standards
- Assisted in the documentation of the wallet versions

COMMUNITY MANAGER

XINFIN.org

2019 - PRESENT

- Developing the African ecosystem for the company
- Established new networks
- Engaging with cooperates and other organisations based in Africa